{
    "question": "Rearrange the sentences become a good dialog.\u00a0*    \ufffc\r\n\r\nA. 1-5-3-4-2\r\n\r\nB. 2-5-3-4-1\r\n\r\nC. 2-4-1-5-3\r\n\r\nD. 1-5-2-4-3\r\n\r\nsecepatnya \r\n\r\n\u200b",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>2-4-1-5-3</p><p></p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>2. Edo : Have you seen real monkey,Udin? i mean not on tv or in a magazine?</p><p>4. Udin : Yes,I have.</p><p>1. Edo : What are they like?</p><p>5. Udin : They&#039;re very friendly and playful.</p><p>3. Edo : Wow! That&#039;s interesting because as far as i know, not all monkeys are friendly. I want to see one too.</p><p></p><p>hope you find this helpful ^\u2022^</p><p></p><p></p>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "analyze-the-texts-below-to-answer-the-question-number-6-text-b-t-801",
            "question": "Analyze the texts below to answer the question number 6!    Text B\r\nText A\r\nI only slept for three hours last night At ten, we heard Last Saturday, my little sister, Dina, did something\r\na cry from Mrs. Wayan's home. She is our next-door funny. She got up very late, at six. She ran fast to the\r\nneighbour She's 70 years old and very weak. She lives bathroom. She thought she would be late to school\r\n. She\r\nalone We went there quickly, and we found her on the forgot it was Saturday. She took a very quick bath, got\r\nfloor\r\n. She just fell She could not move her hands and dressed, took her bag, and ran off to school. She did not\r\nher legs. At 10.30, my parents and I took Mrs. Wayan even have breakfast. After walking for five minutes, she\r\nto hospital. My father and I sat in the front seats. In the noticed that no other children were going to school\r\nback seats, my mum was holding Mrs. Wayan. In the Soon she realized it was Saturday! So, she walked back\r\nemergency room, a doctor examined her. Then, he said\r\nhome. We all laughed at her when she got home. She\r\nMrs. Wayan had to stay in the hospital. When she was also laughed at herself. Then she changed her clothes\r\nalready in the ward, we went home. It was 2 am. and went back to bed! My naughty sister!\r\n sebutkan kata benda dari dua teks tersebut. minimal 3\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>hands, bag, seats, clothes, legs</p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p>smga membantu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>bag,bed,dress</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "what-are-the-facilities-in-the-tourism-objects-957",
            "question": "What are the facilities in the tourism objects?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><u><em><strong>MAKSUDNYA ARTI YA ???</strong></em></u></p><p><u><em><strong></strong></em></u></p><p><strong>ARTI : Apa saja fasilitas yang ada di objek wisata tersebut?</strong></p><p><strong></strong></p><p><strong></strong></p><p><strong></strong></p><p><strong></strong></p><p><strong></strong></p><h2>MAAF KALO SALAH SEMOGA MEMBANTU :D</h2>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "13-they-not-attend-the-party-yesterday-a-do-c-doing-b-did-277",
            "question": "13. They ... not attend the party yesterday    a. Do\r\nc. Doing\r\nb. Did\r\nd. Does\r\n\r\n\r\nbantu jwab ya\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>b. Did</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>B.did</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>v2 karena  sudah terjadi</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "kan-tadi-saya-dikirimi-temen-tc-sebut-nama-nah-ini-cara-jawabn-456",
            "question": "Kan tadi saya dikirimi temen \"tc sebut nama \" nah ini cara jawabnya gimana ya?\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>tc=test contact</p><p></p><p>itu biasanya buat ngetes nomornya masih aktif atau tidak ya jawab aja nama mu</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "complete-the-sentences-use-the-present-continuous-from-of-the-the-417",
            "question": "Complete the sentences use the present continuous from of the the brackets    4. a. my uncle.....( wash ) his car. b.they ..... (listen) to the rock music\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>4. A. My uncle is washing his car. </p><p>B.  They are listening to the rock music. </p><p></p><p>Semoga membantu ^_^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p> </p><p>a.My uncle washed his car.</p><p>b.They listen to rock music.</p><p> </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "the-man-is-mryonohe-is-my-neighborshe-is-asasmridrus-557",
            "question": "The man is Mr.Yono.He is my neighbors.He is as......asMr.idrus\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>Jawaban:</p><p>as nice as </p><p>Penjelasan:</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "our-scholl-is-very-we-can-play-and-do-many-activities-here-we-l-659",
            "question": "Our scholl is very we can play and do many activities here . we love it very mu h\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>sekolah kami sangat kami bisa bermain dan melakukan banyak kegiatan di sini. kami sangat menyukainya</p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>semoga membantu </p><p>                                </p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "9-gambar-disamping-di-gunakanuntuk-a-membuka-gambar-bmenyimpan-767",
            "question": "9. Gambar disamping di gunakanuntuk    a. membuka gambar\r\nb.menyimpan gambar\r\nOpen\r\nc. mencetak gambar\r\ntolong kak besok dikumpulin\u200b",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>maaf ka mana gambar nya </p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p>maaf yyyyyyyyy</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>gambar mana ya\u2639\ufe0f\u2639\ufe0f\u2639\ufe0f</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "fill-i-the-blanks-with-the-form-of-positive-degree-964",
            "question": "Fill i the blanks with the form of positive degree",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p>jawabannya adalah</p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p></p><p>gak tau</p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tuliskan-10-kata-kerja-dalam-bahasa-inggris-dan-artinya-dalam-bah-375",
            "question": "Tuliskan 10 kata kerja dalam bahasa inggris dan artinya dalam bahasa indonesia",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:Fishing memancing, drawing menggambar, reading membaca, writting menulis, taken mengambil , Singing menyanyi,Study belajar , Eating makan , Walking berjalan, Climbing memanjat\n</strong></p><p><strong></strong></p><p><strong></strong></p><p></p><p><strong>Penjelasan:</strong></p><p></p>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<p><strong>Jawaban:</strong></p><p>1. Read artinya Membaca. </p><p>2. Write artinya Menulis. </p><p>3. Speak artinya Berbicara. </p><p>4. Cook artinya Memasak. </p><p>5. Sing artinya Menyanyi. </p><p>6. Bring artinya Membawa. </p><p>7. See artinya Melihat. </p><p>8. Punch artinya Memukul. </p><p>9. Stand artinya Berdiri. </p><p>10. Sit artinya Duduk. </p><p></p><p>Semoga membantu ^_^</p>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}